<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Web Server on SourceMation</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/categories/web-server/</link><description>Recent content in Web Server on SourceMation</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 14:33:46 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sourcemation.com/categories/web-server/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Nginx Stable</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nginx-stable/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 14:33:46 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nginx-stable/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nginx Stable delivers enterprise-grade web serving capabilities with a focus on long-term reliability and consistent
performance across production environments. This stable branch undergoes extensive testing and validation, making it the
preferred choice for mission-critical applications that prioritize stability over cutting-edge features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The stable release branch receives only critical bug fixes and security updates, ensuring predictable behavior and
minimal risk of unexpected changes in production deployments. This approach makes it particularly well-suited for
enterprise environments where stability and reliability take precedence.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Nginx Mainline</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nginx-mainline/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 14:31:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nginx-mainline/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nginx Mainline represents the cutting-edge branch of the world&amp;rsquo;s most popular web server, delivering advanced HTTP
serving, reverse proxy functionality, and sophisticated load balancing capabilities. This version provides access to the
newest features and optimizations as they&amp;rsquo;re developed, making it ideal for environments that require the latest
innovations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Known for its exceptional performance characteristics and minimal resource consumption, Nginx excels at handling
high-concurrency scenarios while maintaining rock-solid stability. The mainline branch receives continuous updates with
new features, protocol improvements, and performance enhancements.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>JRE-21</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jre-21/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:31:38 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jre-21/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;JRE 21 is the Java Runtime Environment derived from the JDK 21
Long-Term Support (LTS) release, and it&amp;rsquo;s intended for end-users or
servers that only need to run pre-compiled Java applications. It
contains the core components, primarily the Java Virtual Machine (JVM)
and core class libraries, but omits development tools like the
compiler (javac). Any application running on JRE 21 gains the benefits
of the JDK 21 platform, including the performance improvements from
the finalization of Virtual Threads and other new language features.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Micronaut</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/micronaut/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:08:47 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/micronaut/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Description: Micronaut is a modern, full-stack framework for the JVM
(supporting Java, Kotlin, and Groovy) designed specifically for
building modular microservices and serverless applications. Its key
differentiator is that it performs dependency injection,
configuration, and aspect-oriented programming at compile time
(Ahead-of-Time compilation) rather than at runtime using reflection.
This results in dramatically faster startup times, a much lower memory
footprint, and makes it an ideal choice for serverless functions and
containerized microservices.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Manageiq</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/manageiq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:59:42 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/manageiq/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;ManageIQ is an open-source cloud management platform (CMP) that
provides a single interface for managing hybrid IT environments. It
discovers and monitors resources across disparate virtualization (like
VMware), private cloud (like OpenStack), and public cloud (like AWS,
Azure) platforms, as well as container platforms like Kubernetes. Its
key features include &amp;ldquo;Insight&amp;rdquo; (discovery, monitoring, analytics),
&amp;ldquo;Control&amp;rdquo; (security, compliance, policy enforcement), and &amp;ldquo;Automate&amp;rdquo;
(provisioning workflows, orchestration). It essentially acts as a
&amp;ldquo;manager of managers,&amp;rdquo; giving administrators a single pane of glass
for governance and automation.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kong</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:47:31 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kong/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Kong is a cloud-native API gateway and platform built on top of Nginx
(specifically OpenResty). It is deployed in front of backend
microservices to act as a single, controllable entry point for all API
traffic. Its core function is to provide a comprehensive security and
management layer, handling tasks like authentication (OAuth2, JWT),
authorization, rate limiting, and traffic transformation via a
&amp;ldquo;plugin&amp;rdquo; architecture. By intercepting and proxying all requests, Kong
also provides critical observability metrics, logs, and traces for
monitoring API performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Helidon</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/helidon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:33:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/helidon/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Helidon is an open-source, cloud-native set of Java libraries from
Oracle for building microservices. It provides two distinct paths for
development. Helidon SE is a lightweight, &amp;ldquo;reactive&amp;rdquo; toolkit that uses
a functional, non-blocking approach (built on Netty) for maximum
performance and a small footprint. Helidon MP is a full implementation
of the Eclipse MicroProfile specification, providing a more
declarative, annotation-driven programming model (similar to Spring
Boot or Micronaut) for enterprise Java developers.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apicast</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apicast/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:04:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apicast/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apicast is the core API gateway component of the 3scale API Management
platform. It is a high-performance, Nginx-based proxy that processes
and controls all inbound API traffic. It intercepts requests,
authenticates them against defined policies (like rate limits, access
keys, or JWTs), and routes them to the correct upstream service. It&amp;rsquo;s
designed to be deployed as a container, managing the secure and
observable flow of communication between API consumers and backend
services.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ArgoCD</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/argocd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:40:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/argocd/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;ArgoCD is a declarative, version-controlled application deployment
tool designed to automate and manage application configurations and
environments. It follows the GitOps pattern, utilizing Git
repositories as the source of truth for defining the desired
application state. Users can specify Kubernetes manifests using
various methods such as kustomize applications, Helm charts, JSONnet
files, or plain directories of YAML/json manifests. ArgoCD automates
the deployment process based on the desired application state defined
in Git repositories, making application deployment and lifecycle
management easy, auditable, and understandable.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Harbor</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/harbor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:55:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/harbor/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Harbor operates as a platform enabling the management of container
repositories in Kubernetes environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Jenkins</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jenkins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 20:49:27 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jenkins/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Jenkins is an open-source automation server used for continuous
integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD) pipelines, enabling
developers to automate building, testing, and deploying software.
Download our ready Helm Charts tailored for Jenkins.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Prometheus</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/prometheus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 19:20:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/prometheus/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Prometheus is a monitoring and alerting system widely used in cloud
and microservices environments. It is an open-source tool that enables
the collection of metrics from various components of IT
infrastructure, such as servers, containers, databases, etc.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Pgadmin</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/pgadmin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 19:06:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/pgadmin/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;pgAdmin functions as an open-source platform for administering and developing PostgreSQL.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Sonarqube</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/sonarqube/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:56:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/sonarqube/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;SonarQube operates as a platform for automatic code quality analysis.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apache Karaf</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-karaf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:12:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-karaf/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Karaf is a lightweight OSGi container that enables easy
deployment, management, and updating of applications and services in
modular environments. It offers flexibility, dynamic module loading,
and clustering, making it an ideal solution for managing applications
in enterprise environments. Karaf is also ideal for Java applications,
enabling modular deployment and management of services in large and
complex environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kibana</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kibana/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:19:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kibana/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Kibana is an advanced tool for data visualization and analysis,
serving as a key component in the Elastic Stack.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apache Camel Karavan</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-camel-karavan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:06:37 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-camel-karavan/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Camel Karavan is a visual extension of Apache Camel that
enables intuitive integration design using Enterprise Integration
Patterns (EIP) through a drag-and-drop interface. This makes it easier
for DevOps teams and developers to create complex data flows and
orchestrate processes, making it ideal for cloud and containerized
environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Gitea</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gitea/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:40:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gitea/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Gitea is a software including Git hosting, code review, team
collaboration, package registry and CI/CD.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Nodejs</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nodejs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:24:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nodejs/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Node.js stands as a dynamic runtime environment, utilizing the V8
engine, specifically crafted for the development of contemporary,
interactive web applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>