<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Security on SourceMation</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/categories/security/</link><description>Recent content in Security on SourceMation</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:31:38 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sourcemation.com/categories/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>JRE-21</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jre-21/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:31:38 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jre-21/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;JRE 21 is the Java Runtime Environment derived from the JDK 21
Long-Term Support (LTS) release, and it&amp;rsquo;s intended for end-users or
servers that only need to run pre-compiled Java applications. It
contains the core components, primarily the Java Virtual Machine (JVM)
and core class libraries, but omits development tools like the
compiler (javac). Any application running on JRE 21 gains the benefits
of the JDK 21 platform, including the performance improvements from
the finalization of Virtual Threads and other new language features.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Micronaut</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/micronaut/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:08:47 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/micronaut/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Description: Micronaut is a modern, full-stack framework for the JVM
(supporting Java, Kotlin, and Groovy) designed specifically for
building modular microservices and serverless applications. Its key
differentiator is that it performs dependency injection,
configuration, and aspect-oriented programming at compile time
(Ahead-of-Time compilation) rather than at runtime using reflection.
This results in dramatically faster startup times, a much lower memory
footprint, and makes it an ideal choice for serverless functions and
containerized microservices.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Manageiq</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/manageiq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:59:42 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/manageiq/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;ManageIQ is an open-source cloud management platform (CMP) that
provides a single interface for managing hybrid IT environments. It
discovers and monitors resources across disparate virtualization (like
VMware), private cloud (like OpenStack), and public cloud (like AWS,
Azure) platforms, as well as container platforms like Kubernetes. Its
key features include &amp;ldquo;Insight&amp;rdquo; (discovery, monitoring, analytics),
&amp;ldquo;Control&amp;rdquo; (security, compliance, policy enforcement), and &amp;ldquo;Automate&amp;rdquo;
(provisioning workflows, orchestration). It essentially acts as a
&amp;ldquo;manager of managers,&amp;rdquo; giving administrators a single pane of glass
for governance and automation.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kong</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:47:31 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kong/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Kong is a cloud-native API gateway and platform built on top of Nginx
(specifically OpenResty). It is deployed in front of backend
microservices to act as a single, controllable entry point for all API
traffic. Its core function is to provide a comprehensive security and
management layer, handling tasks like authentication (OAuth2, JWT),
authorization, rate limiting, and traffic transformation via a
&amp;ldquo;plugin&amp;rdquo; architecture. By intercepting and proxying all requests, Kong
also provides critical observability metrics, logs, and traces for
monitoring API performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Debian 11 Slim</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/debian-11-slim/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:44:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/debian-11-slim/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This is the minimal (&amp;ldquo;slim&amp;rdquo;) variant of the official Docker image for
Debian 11 (codenamed &amp;ldquo;Bullseye&amp;rdquo;), which now serves as the &amp;ldquo;oldstable&amp;rdquo;
release. It&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;ldquo;minbase&amp;rdquo; install of Debian where non-essential
files—such as man pages, documentation, and extra utilities—have been
removed to create the smallest possible image size . This results in a
significantly reduced attack surface and faster container deployments,
making it a highly reliable and secure base OS for containerized
applications that depend on the stability of the Bullseye package set.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Debian 12 Slim</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/debian-12-slim/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:44:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/debian-12-slim/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This is the minimal (&amp;ldquo;slim&amp;rdquo;) variant of the official Docker image for
Debian 12 (codenamed &amp;ldquo;Bookworm&amp;rdquo;), the current stable operating system.
Like other slim images, it&amp;rsquo;s stripped of all non-essential packages
(like documentation and locales) to create the smallest possible base
for secure, fast-deploying applications. It includes the more modern
toolchain from the &amp;ldquo;Bookworm&amp;rdquo; release, which is built on Linux Kernel
6.1 and includes newer packages like Python 3.11 and PostgreSQL 15,
providing a modern yet highly stable OS layer for new cloud-native
services.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Helidon</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/helidon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:33:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/helidon/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Helidon is an open-source, cloud-native set of Java libraries from
Oracle for building microservices. It provides two distinct paths for
development. Helidon SE is a lightweight, &amp;ldquo;reactive&amp;rdquo; toolkit that uses
a functional, non-blocking approach (built on Netty) for maximum
performance and a small footprint. Helidon MP is a full implementation
of the Eclipse MicroProfile specification, providing a more
declarative, annotation-driven programming model (similar to Spring
Boot or Micronaut) for enterprise Java developers.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apicast</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apicast/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:04:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apicast/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apicast is the core API gateway component of the 3scale API Management
platform. It is a high-performance, Nginx-based proxy that processes
and controls all inbound API traffic. It intercepts requests,
authenticates them against defined policies (like rate limits, access
keys, or JWTs), and routes them to the correct upstream service. It&amp;rsquo;s
designed to be deployed as a container, managing the secure and
observable flow of communication between API consumers and backend
services.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Greenplum DB</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/greenplum-db/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:35:33 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/greenplum-db/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Greenplum Database (GPDB) is an open-source database optimized for
data analytics in distributed environments, utilizing a massively
parallel processing (MPP) architecture. It enables the simultaneous
processing of large datasets across multiple nodes, providing high
performance and scalability, and supports advanced business analytics
and big data processing.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Sealed Secrets</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/sealed-secrets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:21:43 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/sealed-secrets/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Sealed Secret is a tool used in the Kubernetes ecosystem for securely
storing sensitive data, such as passwords or private keys.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>[X?] External Secrets</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/external-secrets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:07:34 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/external-secrets/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;External Secrets Operator is a tool for Kubernetes environments that
enables integration with various external secret management systems.
It operates by retrieving data from these external sources using their
APIs and automatically injecting this data into Kubernetes Secret
resources. Its goal is to facilitate the synchronization and
management of secrets between external systems and Kubernetes.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Harbor</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/harbor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:55:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/harbor/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Harbor operates as a platform enabling the management of container
repositories in Kubernetes environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Elasticsearch</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/elasticsearch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:34:46 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/elasticsearch/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Elasticsearch is a powerful search and data analysis engine that
enables processing, indexing, and analysis of large datasets in
real-time. It functions as a central component of the Elastic Stack,
which also includes Kibana for data visualization and Logstash for log
processing. Elasticsearch is utilized in various fields such as log
analysis, IT infrastructure monitoring, business data analysis,
content searching, and information security.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Trivy</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/trivy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 19:47:26 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/trivy/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Trivy is a vulnerability analysis tool for containers. It is a
vulnerability scanner that automatically scans container images and
reports discovered security vulnerabilities and other potential
threats.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Sonarqube</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/sonarqube/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:56:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/sonarqube/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;SonarQube operates as a platform for automatic code quality analysis.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kyverno</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kyverno/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:37:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kyverno/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Kyverno is an open source policy engine for Kubernetes, enabling the
definition, management, and enforcement of security and compliance
policies within a Kubernetes cluster.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Istio</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/istio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:30:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/istio/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Istio is a platform for managing traffic, securing, and monitoring
services in microservices environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ClickHouse</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/clickhouse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:31:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/clickhouse/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;ClickHouse is an open-source, columnar database specializing in
ultra-fast analytics and real-time processing of large data volumes.
Optimized for handling massive datasets, ClickHouse enables
lightning-fast execution of complex SQL queries, making it ideal for
companies focused on big data and business analytics. It supports
cluster processing, allowing efficient querying of distributed data
and real-time report generation.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apache Karaf</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-karaf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:12:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-karaf/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Karaf is a lightweight OSGi container that enables easy
deployment, management, and updating of applications and services in
modular environments. It offers flexibility, dynamic module loading,
and clustering, making it an ideal solution for managing applications
in enterprise environments. Karaf is also ideal for Java applications,
enabling modular deployment and management of services in large and
complex environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Redis</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/redis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:56:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/redis/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Redis functions as an efficient, non-relational database management
system that stores data in a key-value structure within the primary
storage of the server, ensuring swift access to information.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apache Doris</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-doris/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:43:27 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-doris/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Doris is a distributed, open-source OLAP database optimized for
high performance and ease of use. With its MPP (Massively Parallel
Processing) model, it supports real-time analytical and operational
queries, making it ideal for big data applications, recommendation
systems, and business dashboards. Apache Doris offers
user-friendliness and integration with popular analytics tools,
enabling quick deployment and efficient report generation.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kibana</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kibana/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:19:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kibana/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Kibana is an advanced tool for data visualization and analysis,
serving as a key component in the Elastic Stack.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ActiveMQ</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-activemq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:56:03 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-activemq/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;ActiveMQ is an open-source message queuing system that supports
protocols such as JMS, STOMP, MQTT, and AMQP. It enables asynchronous
message exchange in distributed environments, providing reliability,
scalability, and ease of use. Ideal for cloud and microservice
applications, ActiveMQ offers high availability and support for
clustering and message replication, enabling the creation of
event-driven applications and system integration.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Gitea</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gitea/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:40:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gitea/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Gitea is a software including Git hosting, code review, team
collaboration, package registry and CI/CD.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Starrocks</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/starrocks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:34:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/starrocks/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;StarRocks is a modern MPP (Massively Parallel Processing) database
designed for advanced analytics with ultra-fast OLAP queries. It
enables simultaneous processing of historical and operational data,
making it ideal for applications requiring real-time analytics.
StarRocks combines the flexibility of NoSQL with the performance of
SQL, supporting various data formats and integrating with popular
analytics tools. It ensures high query performance and supports
complex analyses.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Databend</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/databend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:18:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/databend/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Databend is an open-source, Rust-based cloud data warehouse offering
high performance for large datasets, with features like Time Travel,
Multi Catalog, and seamless scalability across various object storage
solutions.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Neuvector</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/neuvector/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 11:34:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/neuvector/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;NeuVector is a platform for securing containers and microservices operating in cloud-based environments, including
Kubernetes clusters. It provides monitoring, threat detection, and security incident response capabilities. Download
our ready Helm Charts tailored for NeuVector.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apache Servicemix</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-servicemix/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:54:31 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-servicemix/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;</description></item><item><title>Cert-manager</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cert-manager/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:42:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cert-manager/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cert-manager is a Kubernetes tool that automates the issuance, renewal, and management of TLS certificates using various
providers like Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt. Download our ready Helm Charts tailored for KubeArmor.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>