<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Extensions on SourceMation</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/categories/extensions/</link><description>Recent content in Extensions on SourceMation</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 13:11:55 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/categories/extensions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Openapi Generator CLI</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/openapi-generator-cli/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 13:11:55 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/openapi-generator-cli/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The OpenAPI Generator CLI is a powerful command-line utility that automates the creation of client libraries, server
stubs, and API documentation from OpenAPI specifications. This tool significantly accelerates development workflows by
generating consistent, well-structured code across multiple programming languages and frameworks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SourceMation&amp;rsquo;s distribution comes pre-configured with a secure user environment and includes an enhanced CLI script for
simplified version management. The container is built with security best practices, running under a non-root user
account to minimize potential attack vectors. Our automated build process ensures you receive the latest stable release
with all necessary dependencies properly configured for immediate use.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>JRE-21</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/jre-21/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:31:38 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/jre-21/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;JRE 21 is the Java Runtime Environment derived from the JDK 21
Long-Term Support (LTS) release, and it&amp;rsquo;s intended for end-users or
servers that only need to run pre-compiled Java applications. It
contains the core components, primarily the Java Virtual Machine (JVM)
and core class libraries, but omits development tools like the
compiler (javac). Any application running on JRE 21 gains the benefits
of the JDK 21 platform, including the performance improvements from
the finalization of Virtual Threads and other new language features.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>RabbitMQ Management</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/rabbitmq-4-management/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:39:56 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/rabbitmq-4-management/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RabbitMQ (ver 4.x) Management delivers enterprise-grade message brokering with an intuitive web interface for real-time
monitoring and administrative control. This solution combines robust AMQP message processing with advanced management
features including queue analytics, connection tracking, and cluster health monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The management interface enables administrators to visualize message flows, configure exchanges and bindings, and manage
user permissions through a responsive web dashboard. Built for production environments, it supports high-throughput
messaging scenarios while maintaining operational transparency and control.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Redis Exporter</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/redis-exporter/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:16:03 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/redis-exporter/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Redis Exporter is a specialized monitoring tool that bridges Redis databases with Prometheus-based observability
platforms. It continuously collects comprehensive metrics including memory usage, connection statistics, command
execution rates, and replication status from Redis instances.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The exporter transforms Redis INFO command output and custom queries into Prometheus-compatible metrics, enabling
detailed performance analysis and automated alerting. It supports both standalone Redis servers and clustered
deployments, making it essential for maintaining visibility into Redis infrastructure health and performance trends.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Redis Operator</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/redis-operator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:11:13 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/redis-operator/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Redis Operator is a cloud-native solution that automates the deployment and management of Redis instances on Kubernetes
platforms. It supports both standalone and clustered Redis configurations, handling complex operations like scaling,
backup, and failover through declarative Kubernetes resources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The operator integrates seamlessly with Kubernetes ecosystem tools and provides comprehensive monitoring through Redis
exporters. It enables teams to focus on application development while ensuring Redis infrastructure remains highly
available and optimally configured across cloud and on-premises environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Redis Sentinel</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/redis-sentinel/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:58:05 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/redis-sentinel/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Redis Sentinel is a high availability solution that monitors Redis deployments and automatically handles failover
scenarios. It ensures continuous service by detecting master failures and promoting replicas through distributed
consensus among Sentinel nodes. Sentinel makes quorum-based decisions to maintain system integrity and prevent
split-brain situations.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GP Backup</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/gpbackup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:30:13 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/gpbackup/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GPBackup is an efficient tool for managing backups in Greenplum
Database. It allows the creation of full and incremental backups of
entire databases as well as selected tables. With advanced data
compression and segmentation, it ensures fast backup creation and the
ability to restore data to any point in time.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GP Diskquota</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/gp-diskquota/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 20:34:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/gp-diskquota/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Diskquota is an extension that provides disk usage enforcement for
database objects in Greenplum DB. Currently it supports to set quota
limit on schema and role in a given database and limit the amount of
disk space that a schema or a role can use.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>[X] Postgis</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/postgis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:26:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/postgis/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;PostGIS is an extension for PostgreSQL that enables processing and
analysis of geospatial data, in compliance with OGC standards.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Gpbackup S3</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/gpbackup-s3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:20:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/gpbackup-s3/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GPBackup-S3 is a tool for automatic backups of Greenplum Database with
Amazon S3 integration. It enables easy storage, restoration, and
verification of full and incremental backups in a secure, scalable
cloud. This is an ideal solution for organizations looking to
efficiently manage data in the cloud.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>[X] Pgbadger</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/pgbadger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:31:43 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/pgbadger/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;pgBadger is a PostgreSQL log analyzer that generates detailed reports based on log files.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>[X] Pglogical</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/pglogical/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:28:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/pglogical/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;PgLogical is an extension for PostgreSQL that enables logical data
replication between instances, offering selective data replication and
support for migrations and synchronization between databases.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>[X] Apache Camel</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/apache-camel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:10:41 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/apache-camel/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Camel is a flexible, open-source integration framework that
enables the creation of complex data exchange processes across
different systems. Camel excels in microservice integration and
business process automation, allowing for easy creation of flexible
data flows.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apache Camel Karavan</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/apache-camel-karavan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:06:37 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/apache-camel-karavan/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Camel Karavan is a visual extension of Apache Camel that
enables intuitive integration design using Enterprise Integration
Patterns (EIP) through a drag-and-drop interface. This makes it easier
for DevOps teams and developers to create complex data flows and
orchestrate processes, making it ideal for cloud and containerized
environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>[X] Apache Felix</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/apache-felix/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:50:23 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/apache-felix/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Felix is an OSGi implementation for building modular Java
applications with dynamic component management and support for
microservices.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>[X] Gp Geospatial</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/gp-geospatial/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 14:40:34 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/gp-geospatial/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GeoSpatial is a technology for analyzing and visualizing geospatial
data, used for creating maps, managing locations, and spatial analysis
in location-based applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GP PXF</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/gp-pxf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 14:11:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/gp-pxf/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;An extension for Greenplum Database that enables access to data from
various sources, such as HDFS, Amazon S3, and NoSQL databases, without
the need to transfer them. It supports data formats like CSV, Parquet,
and Avro, facilitating big data integration and analysis within a
single environment&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Cert-manager</title><link>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/cert-manager/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:42:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.github.io/sourcemation/catalog/cert-manager/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cert-manager is a Kubernetes tool that automates the issuance, renewal, and management of TLS certificates using various
providers like Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt. Download our ready Helm Charts tailored for KubeArmor.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>