<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Risk Landscape on SourceMation</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/tags/risk-landscape/</link><description>Recent content in Risk Landscape on SourceMation</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 14:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sourcemation.com/tags/risk-landscape/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Open Source Software: A Guide to Its Unique Risk Landscape</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/blog/open-source-software-a-guide-to-its-unique-risk-landscape/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/blog/open-source-software-a-guide-to-its-unique-risk-landscape/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="in-todays-fast-paced-technological-landscape-nearly-every-application-and-system-relies-on-open-source-software-components-open-source-not-only-unlocks-vast-possibilities-enables-free-modification-and-development-and-accelerates-access-to-innovation-but-also-introduces-new-challenges-related-to-security-regulatory-compliance-and-meeting-organizational-requirements-this-article-examines-these-issues-by-exploring-current-trends-and-challenges-in-risk-assessment-when-using-open-source-software"&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced technological landscape, nearly every application and system relies on open source software components. Open source not only unlocks vast possibilities, enables free modification and development, and accelerates access to innovation, but also introduces new challenges related to security, regulatory compliance, and meeting organizational requirements. This article examines these issues by exploring current trends and challenges in risk assessment when using open source software.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Open source software is more than just publicly available source code. It is also a philosophy and a community that has revolutionized traditional business models and transformed the technological landscape. A defining feature of open source is its openness to modification, improvement, and customization by a broad community of developers. Open source code offers countless opportunities and has applications across various sectors – from IT and finance to healthcare, industry, and defense.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>