<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Sourcemation</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/categories/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Sourcemation</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 11:50:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sourcemation.com/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EZD RP: An Electronic Document Management System for Public Administration</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/blog/ezd-rp-electronic-document-management-system-for-public-administration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/blog/ezd-rp-electronic-document-management-system-for-public-administration/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="ezd-rp-an-electronic-document-management-system-for-public-administration"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EZD RP: An Electronic Document Management System for Public Administration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;EZD RP&lt;/strong&gt; system is a comprehensive electronic document management system designed for public administration units.
It handles both incoming and outgoing documents, as well as the compilation and archiving of case files. Starting on
January 1, 2028, all public entities and their subordinate units will be required to implement an EZD-class system and
perform clerical tasks within it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id="system-development-and-support"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;System Development and Support&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The EZD RP system was created as part of the IT project &amp;ldquo;EZD RP - Electronic Document Management in Public
Administration.&amp;rdquo; The project was implemented by the &lt;strong&gt;National Research Institute NASK&lt;/strong&gt; in collaboration with the
Podlaskie Voivodeship and under the supervision of the Chancellery of the Prime Minister (KPRM).&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kyverno and Kubernetes Admission Controllers</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/blog/kyverno-installation-management/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/blog/kyverno-installation-management/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/strong&gt;, the leading container orchestration platform, brings
immense flexibility but also new security challenges. As adoption grows,
robust security practices are no longer optional they&amp;rsquo;re critical.
While it&amp;rsquo;s possible to rely on individual users to adopt good
practices, this approach is often unrealistic. Security measures often
add complexity to developers&amp;rsquo; workflows, raising the barrier for
project onboarding and delivery. From their perspective, ensuring the
application functions correctly is the top priority, while security
often takes a back seat. An effective solution is a tool that
automatically verifies which objects are being applied to the cluster
and how. In other words, Kubernetes administrators should be empowered
to automatically control what is applied. One promising solution is
&lt;strong&gt;Kyverno&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kubernetes vs. Rancher and OpenShift - What's the Difference?</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/blog/kubernets-vs-rancher-and-openshift-whats-the-difference/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/blog/kubernets-vs-rancher-and-openshift-whats-the-difference/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When planning to implement containerization in an organization, we often choose to use Kubernetes. This choice is fully justified because Kubernetes is a well-established platform in the market, available under an open-source license, valued for its popularity, flexibility, security, and ease of management. Such an impression may arise after studying many materials about the benefits of containerization using Kubernetes. However, it is worth checking whether these positive features are truly fully aligned with reality. Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the basics: What is Kubernetes, and what underpins its popularity? When is it worth considering Rancher or OpenShift?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Let's help the European Union enter its technological maturity</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/blog/european-union-software-maturity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/blog/european-union-software-maturity/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Under heavy geopolitical pressure, China is rapidly gaining independence from external intellectual property. This is evident in open source software, the backbone of over 90 percent of software developed worldwide. Initiatives like OSChina are spearheading technology internalization and driving local innovation. Is the European Union keeping pace? The world is rapidly fragmenting and becoming multipolar, with no space for the complacent. In the dynamic realms of business and politics, there&amp;rsquo;s no room for complacency-only proactive action will ensure our technological independence. The time to act is now.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Open Source Software: A Guide to Its Unique Risk Landscape</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/blog/open-source-software-a-guide-to-its-unique-risk-landscape/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/blog/open-source-software-a-guide-to-its-unique-risk-landscape/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="in-todays-fast-paced-technological-landscape-nearly-every-application-and-system-relies-on-open-source-software-components-open-source-not-only-unlocks-vast-possibilities-enables-free-modification-and-development-and-accelerates-access-to-innovation-but-also-introduces-new-challenges-related-to-security-regulatory-compliance-and-meeting-organizational-requirements-this-article-examines-these-issues-by-exploring-current-trends-and-challenges-in-risk-assessment-when-using-open-source-software"&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced technological landscape, nearly every application and system relies on open source software components. Open source not only unlocks vast possibilities, enables free modification and development, and accelerates access to innovation, but also introduces new challenges related to security, regulatory compliance, and meeting organizational requirements. This article examines these issues by exploring current trends and challenges in risk assessment when using open source software.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Open source software is more than just publicly available source code. It is also a philosophy and a community that has revolutionized traditional business models and transformed the technological landscape. A defining feature of open source is its openness to modification, improvement, and customization by a broad community of developers. Open source code offers countless opportunities and has applications across various sectors – from IT and finance to healthcare, industry, and defense.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>