<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Software Catalog on SourceMation</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/</link><description>Recent content in Software Catalog on SourceMation</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 14:40:02 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sourcemation.com/catalog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>golang-1.25</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/golang-1.25/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 14:40:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/golang-1.25/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This image features Go 1.25, the stable release of the Go programming language, designed to enhance performance, it
was released August 2025.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The most significant updates in Go 1.25 are heavily focused on performance and
developer tooling. A major highlight is the introduction of a new experimental
garbage collector that promises a &lt;strong&gt;10-40% reduction in overhead, greatly
boosting efficiency for memory-intensive applications&lt;/strong&gt;. For modern cloud-native
environments, &lt;code&gt;GOMAXPROCS&lt;/code&gt; is now container-aware, automatically adjusting to
cgroup CPU limits to improve resource utilization in platforms like Kubernetes.
Furthermore, the release introduces the new &lt;code&gt;testing/synctest&lt;/code&gt; package, which
simplifies the process of writing reliable tests for concurrent code by
providing a virtualized time environment, enhancing code quality and
robustness.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Nginx Stable</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nginx-stable/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 14:33:46 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nginx-stable/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nginx Stable delivers enterprise-grade web serving capabilities with a focus on long-term reliability and consistent
performance across production environments. This stable branch undergoes extensive testing and validation, making it the
preferred choice for mission-critical applications that prioritize stability over cutting-edge features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The stable release branch receives only critical bug fixes and security updates, ensuring predictable behavior and
minimal risk of unexpected changes in production deployments. This approach makes it particularly well-suited for
enterprise environments where stability and reliability take precedence.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Nginx Mainline</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nginx-mainline/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 14:31:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nginx-mainline/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nginx Mainline represents the cutting-edge branch of the world&amp;rsquo;s most popular web server, delivering advanced HTTP
serving, reverse proxy functionality, and sophisticated load balancing capabilities. This version provides access to the
newest features and optimizations as they&amp;rsquo;re developed, making it ideal for environments that require the latest
innovations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Known for its exceptional performance characteristics and minimal resource consumption, Nginx excels at handling
high-concurrency scenarios while maintaining rock-solid stability. The mainline branch receives continuous updates with
new features, protocol improvements, and performance enhancements.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Mosquitto</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/mosquitto/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 14:26:38 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/mosquitto/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eclipse Mosquitto is a widely-adopted open-source MQTT broker that serves as the backbone for countless IoT deployments
worldwide. Developed under the Eclipse Foundation, it implements the MQTT protocol versions 5.0, 3.1.1, and 3.1, making
it compatible with virtually any MQTT client application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The broker is renowned for its lightweight architecture and exceptional performance, capable of handling thousands of
concurrent connections while maintaining minimal memory usage. Mosquitto supports advanced features including message
persistence, SSL/TLS encryption, bridge connections, and flexible authentication mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>NodeJS 20</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nodejs-20/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 13:39:33 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nodejs-20/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Node.js 20 offers a mature and reliable platform for JavaScript development, supporting everything from lightweight
utilities to enterprise-grade applications. Its proven stability and extensive ecosystem make it an excellent choice for
production environments requiring long-term support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SourceMation&amp;rsquo;s Node.js 20 distribution is built on our hardened Debian 12 Slim base image and includes Yarn Classic
package manager for enhanced dependency management. This build-optimized version contains all necessary compilation
tools and development packages, ensuring seamless integration with complex Node.js projects that require native module
compilation and advanced build workflows.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>NodeJS 22</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nodejs-22/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 13:36:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nodejs-22/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Node.js 22 provides a robust foundation for developing modern JavaScript applications across diverse use cases, from
simple automation scripts to complex enterprise platforms. Its asynchronous, event-driven architecture enables efficient
handling of concurrent operations while maintaining excellent performance characteristics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Node.js 22 container builds upon the secure SourceMation Debian 12 Slim base image and includes Yarn Classic for
streamlined dependency management. The distribution is optimized for development workflows and includes compilation
tools necessary for building native modules, making it ideal for professional development environments where build
reproducibility is essential.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>NodeJS 24</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nodejs-24/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 13:33:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nodejs-24/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Node.js 24 delivers exceptional performance for modern JavaScript applications, enabling developers to build everything
from APIs to real-time applications using a single language across the entire stack. Its event-driven, non-blocking I/O
model makes it particularly well-suited for data-intensive applications that run across distributed devices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SourceMation&amp;rsquo;s Node.js 24 distribution comes bundled with Yarn Classic package manager and essential build tools on our
secure Debian 12 Slim foundation. This comprehensive setup provides developers with everything needed for advanced
Node.js development workflows, including compilation capabilities and dependency management. While this results in a
larger image size, it ensures complete functionality for professional development environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Openapi Generator CLI</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/openapi-generator-cli/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 13:11:55 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/openapi-generator-cli/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The OpenAPI Generator CLI is a powerful command-line utility that automates the creation of client libraries, server
stubs, and API documentation from OpenAPI specifications. This tool significantly accelerates development workflows by
generating consistent, well-structured code across multiple programming languages and frameworks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SourceMation&amp;rsquo;s distribution comes pre-configured with a secure user environment and includes an enhanced CLI script for
simplified version management. The container is built with security best practices, running under a non-root user
account to minimize potential attack vectors. Our automated build process ensures you receive the latest stable release
with all necessary dependencies properly configured for immediate use.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Postgres 16</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/postgres-16/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 13:05:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/postgres-16/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PostgreSQL 16 represents a mature and battle-tested database solution that has evolved through decades of continuous
innovation and community contribution. This version combines advanced SQL capabilities with exceptional stability,
making it the preferred choice for mission-critical applications across industries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SourceMation&amp;rsquo;s PostgreSQL 16 distribution is compiled using our secure automated build system on the latest Debian 12
Slim foundation. Each build undergoes rigorous verification processes including cryptographic validation of source
materials, ensuring you receive a hardened and trustworthy database platform. Regular maintenance updates keep your
installation current with the latest security patches and performance improvements.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Postgres 17</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/postgres-17/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 13:03:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/postgres-17/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PostgreSQL stands as one of the most sophisticated open-source database systems available, offering enterprise-level
capabilities with over three decades of continuous development. Known for its exceptional reliability, extensibility,
and standards compliance, it supports both SQL relational and JSON non-relational querying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our PostgreSQL 17 container is meticulously built by SourceMation&amp;rsquo;s automated infrastructure using the latest stable
release. Running on our optimized Debian 12 Slim base image, this distribution ensures minimal attack surface while
maintaining full functionality. The build pipeline includes cryptographic verification of all source components,
delivering a secure and trustworthy database solution for production environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Python 3.12</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/python-3.12/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 13:00:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/python-3.12/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Python delivers exceptional productivity through its intuitive syntax and comprehensive standard library, empowering
developers across web development, data analysis, and automation projects. The language&amp;rsquo;s design philosophy emphasizes
code readability and developer efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Python 3.12 build is automatically compiled and maintained by SourceMation&amp;rsquo;s secure infrastructure. Each release
includes the latest security patches and comes pre-configured with pip, providing you with a reliable and up-to-date
Python environment for your projects.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>JRE-21</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jre-21/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:31:38 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jre-21/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;JRE 21 is the Java Runtime Environment derived from the JDK 21
Long-Term Support (LTS) release, and it&amp;rsquo;s intended for end-users or
servers that only need to run pre-compiled Java applications. It
contains the core components, primarily the Java Virtual Machine (JVM)
and core class libraries, but omits development tools like the
compiler (javac). Any application running on JRE 21 gains the benefits
of the JDK 21 platform, including the performance improvements from
the finalization of Virtual Threads and other new language features.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>JDK-21</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jdk-21/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:31:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jdk-21/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;JDK 21 is the official Java Development Kit for the Java 21 Long-Term
Support (LTS) release, designed for application developers. It
includes all the tools needed to compile, debug, and run Java
applications, such as the javac compiler and the Java Virtual Machine.
This version is critically important as it finalizes several major
features from Project Loom, most notably Virtual Threads, which
fundamentally simplifies the development of high-throughput concurrent
applications. It also introduces other key features like Sequenced
Collections, Scoped Values, and enhanced Pattern Matching.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Micronaut</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/micronaut/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:08:47 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/micronaut/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Description: Micronaut is a modern, full-stack framework for the JVM
(supporting Java, Kotlin, and Groovy) designed specifically for
building modular microservices and serverless applications. Its key
differentiator is that it performs dependency injection,
configuration, and aspect-oriented programming at compile time
(Ahead-of-Time compilation) rather than at runtime using reflection.
This results in dramatically faster startup times, a much lower memory
footprint, and makes it an ideal choice for serverless functions and
containerized microservices.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Maven</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/maven/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:03:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/maven/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Maven is a foundational software project management and build
automation tool. Using a central XML configuration file (the pom.xml),
Maven manages all project dependencies (downloading required libraries
from repositories) and executes a standardized build lifecycle (e.g.,
compile, test, package, install, deploy). This
convention-over-configuration approach simplifies the build process,
making it reproducible and standard across all Java-based projects.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Manageiq</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/manageiq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:59:42 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/manageiq/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;ManageIQ is an open-source cloud management platform (CMP) that
provides a single interface for managing hybrid IT environments. It
discovers and monitors resources across disparate virtualization (like
VMware), private cloud (like OpenStack), and public cloud (like AWS,
Azure) platforms, as well as container platforms like Kubernetes. Its
key features include &amp;ldquo;Insight&amp;rdquo; (discovery, monitoring, analytics),
&amp;ldquo;Control&amp;rdquo; (security, compliance, policy enforcement), and &amp;ldquo;Automate&amp;rdquo;
(provisioning workflows, orchestration). It essentially acts as a
&amp;ldquo;manager of managers,&amp;rdquo; giving administrators a single pane of glass
for governance and automation.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kubectl</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kubectl/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:55:26 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kubectl/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;kubectl is the primary command-line interface (CLI) used to
communicate with and manage a Kubernetes cluster. It communicates with
the Kubernetes API server to execute commands. Administrators and
developers use this utility for nearly all cluster operations,
including deploying applications (using .yaml manifests), checking the
status and logs of running pods (observability), managing node health,
and configuring all Kubernetes resources like services, deployments,
and secrets.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kong</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:47:31 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kong/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Kong is a cloud-native API gateway and platform built on top of Nginx
(specifically OpenResty). It is deployed in front of backend
microservices to act as a single, controllable entry point for all API
traffic. Its core function is to provide a comprehensive security and
management layer, handling tasks like authentication (OAuth2, JWT),
authorization, rate limiting, and traffic transformation via a
&amp;ldquo;plugin&amp;rdquo; architecture. By intercepting and proxying all requests, Kong
also provides critical observability metrics, logs, and traces for
monitoring API performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Debian 11 Slim</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/debian-11-slim/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:44:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/debian-11-slim/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This is the minimal (&amp;ldquo;slim&amp;rdquo;) variant of the official Docker image for
Debian 11 (codenamed &amp;ldquo;Bullseye&amp;rdquo;), which now serves as the &amp;ldquo;oldstable&amp;rdquo;
release. It&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;ldquo;minbase&amp;rdquo; install of Debian where non-essential
files—such as man pages, documentation, and extra utilities—have been
removed to create the smallest possible image size . This results in a
significantly reduced attack surface and faster container deployments,
making it a highly reliable and secure base OS for containerized
applications that depend on the stability of the Bullseye package set.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Debian 12 Slim</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/debian-12-slim/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:44:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/debian-12-slim/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This is the minimal (&amp;ldquo;slim&amp;rdquo;) variant of the official Docker image for
Debian 12 (codenamed &amp;ldquo;Bookworm&amp;rdquo;), the current stable operating system.
Like other slim images, it&amp;rsquo;s stripped of all non-essential packages
(like documentation and locales) to create the smallest possible base
for secure, fast-deploying applications. It includes the more modern
toolchain from the &amp;ldquo;Bookworm&amp;rdquo; release, which is built on Linux Kernel
6.1 and includes newer packages like Python 3.11 and PostgreSQL 15,
providing a modern yet highly stable OS layer for new cloud-native
services.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Helidon</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/helidon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:33:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/helidon/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Helidon is an open-source, cloud-native set of Java libraries from
Oracle for building microservices. It provides two distinct paths for
development. Helidon SE is a lightweight, &amp;ldquo;reactive&amp;rdquo; toolkit that uses
a functional, non-blocking approach (built on Netty) for maximum
performance and a small footprint. Helidon MP is a full implementation
of the Eclipse MicroProfile specification, providing a more
declarative, annotation-driven programming model (similar to Spring
Boot or Micronaut) for enterprise Java developers.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Python 3.11</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/python-3.11/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:57:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/python-3.11/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Python excels as a versatile programming language that combines elegant syntax with powerful capabilities, making it an
ideal choice for everything from web applications to machine learning projects. Its emphasis on code clarity and
extensive library ecosystem enables rapid development across multiple domains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Python 3.11 distribution is automatically built from verified source code by SourceMation&amp;rsquo;s secure build
infrastructure. This release receives consistent patch updates and includes pip pre-installed for convenient package
management. Built on our optimized Debian 12 slim base image, it provides a secure, self-contained Python environment
with cryptographic verification throughout the build process.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Python 3.13</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/python-3.13/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:57:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/python-3.13/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Python stands out as a highly readable and versatile programming language, making it ideal for diverse applications from
web development to machine learning. Its clean syntax and rich library ecosystem enable developers to build robust
solutions efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Python 3.13 distribution is built from the latest sources by SourceMation&amp;rsquo;s automation infrastructure. This version
receives regular patch updates and includes pip for streamlined package management, ensuring you have the most current
and secure Python environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Erlang</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/erlang/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:55:54 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/erlang/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Erlang is a functional programming language and runtime environment
(known as OTP - Open Telecom Platform) built by Ericsson. Its entire
design is centered on &amp;ldquo;massive concurrency&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;high availability.&amp;rdquo;
It achieves this by using lightweight, isolated processes (not OS
threads) that communicate via messages (the &amp;ldquo;Actor Model&amp;rdquo;). This &amp;ldquo;let
it crash&amp;rdquo; philosophy allows for the creation of fault-tolerant systems
where failures in one part do not bring down the entire application,
making it ideal for telecom (its original use), messaging (like
RabbitMQ), and other distributed, high-availability backend systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>golang-1.23</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/golang-1.23/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:51:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/golang-1.23/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This is the Go programming language, version 1.23 (released August
2024). This major release finalized a significant new language
feature: range-over functions, which allows iterating over function
calls in for&amp;hellip;range loops, greatly simplifying iterative code. This
version also brought major updates to its toolchain, significantly
reducing the build time overhead for Profile-Guided Optimization (PGO)
and fixing a long-standing source of memory leaks by garbage
collecting time.Timer and time.Ticker objects even if their Stop
methods are not called.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>golang-1.24</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/golang-1.24/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:51:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/golang-1.24/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This is the Go programming language, version 1.24 (released February
2025). This release focused heavily on runtime and toolchain
performance. Key features include a new implementation for maps based
on Swiss Tables, resulting in faster map operations and 2-3% lower CPU
overhead on average. For developers, it introduced a new tool
directive in go.mod to track tool dependencies (replacing the old
tools.go pattern), added a new testing.B.Loop method for simpler
benchmarking, and expanded the vet tool to find common errors in test
functions.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Python 3.8</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/python-3.8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:50:43 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/python-3.8/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security Notice: Python 3.8 reached end-of-life in October 2024 and no longer receives security updates. This version
should only be used for legacy system maintenance where immediate migration is not possible.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This containerized Python 3.8 environment serves organizations requiring backward compatibility for mission-critical
applications that cannot be immediately upgraded. While the underlying system components receive regular security
patches, the Python interpreter itself remains at version 3.8 to maintain application compatibility.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Quarkus</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/quarkus/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:43:54 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/quarkus/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quarkus revolutionizes Java development by delivering lightning-fast application startup and minimal resource footprint
for modern cloud architectures. This Kubernetes-native framework combines traditional Java ecosystem compatibility with
cutting-edge performance optimizations, enabling developers to build reactive microservices that scale efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The framework features live coding capabilities that accelerate development cycles. Quarkus seamlessly integrates with
popular Java libraries
and frameworks, making it ideal for serverless deployments and high-density container orchestration scenarios. It can
be used with GraalVM to compile applications into native executables, further enhancing performance and reducing latency
in
cloud environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GCC-13</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gcc-13/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:41:14 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gcc-13/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GCC 13, the GNU Compiler Collection, is the foundational toolchain for
most Linux systems. This version significantly expanded its language
support by introducing an initial front-end for the Rust programming
language. It also solidified its C++ support by completing many C++20
features and introducing initial capabilities from the C++23 standard.
As a critical component, it takes source code from these languages
(plus C, Fortran, etc.) and translates it into optimized machine code,
while adding improved static analysis tools (like SARIF diagnostics)
for all developers.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GCC-14</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gcc-14/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:41:14 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gcc-14/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GCC 14, the GNU Compiler Collection, continues its role as the core
compiler for the GNU project. This release is notable for its
significant progress on the C++23 standard, implementing new features
like static operator() and import std;. It also enhances its support
for modern hardware, introducing improved code generation for new Arm
and RISC-V processor extensions, and expands its parallelism
capabilities with deeper support for the OpenMP 5.1 and 5.2 standards.
It translates human-readable source code into the optimized machine
code required for all open-source compilation.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GCC-15</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gcc-15/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:41:14 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gcc-15/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GCC 15, the GNU Compiler Collection, serves as the critical compiler
toolchain for most Linux distributions. This version marks a major
milestone by officially changing the default C language standard from
GNU17 to GNU23. It also dramatically expands its language support by
introducing a new front-end for the COBOL programming language. As a
core component of open-source development, it translates source code
into optimized machine code while providing powerful new features like
incremental Link-Time Optimization (LTO) to speed up builds.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GCC-16</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gcc-16/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:41:14 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gcc-16/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GCC 16, representing the current development trunk of the GNU Compiler
Collection, is the next major iteration of the foundational
open-source toolchain. As the default compiler for the Linux
ecosystem, its development is focused on pushing language standards
forward, primarily by introducing experimental support for the
upcoming C++26 standard (such as std::function_ref). It continues to
be the critical utility that translates human-readable C, C++, and
other languages into the optimized machine code that powers the
open-source world, with a focus on new optimization techniques and
hardware support.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>RabbitMQ Management</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/rabbitmq-4-management/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:39:56 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/rabbitmq-4-management/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RabbitMQ (ver 4.x) Management delivers enterprise-grade message brokering with an intuitive web interface for real-time
monitoring and administrative control. This solution combines robust AMQP message processing with advanced management
features including queue analytics, connection tracking, and cluster health monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The management interface enables administrators to visualize message flows, configure exchanges and bindings, and manage
user permissions through a responsive web dashboard. Built for production environments, it supports high-throughput
messaging scenarios while maintaining operational transparency and control.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>CloudNativePG-16</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cnpg-16/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:30:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cnpg-16/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;CloudNativePG (CNPG) is a Kubernetes operator designed by PostgreSQL
experts to manage PostgreSQL database workloads natively on
Kubernetes. It covers the entire operational lifecycle, automatically
managing database deployment, high-availability configurations
(primary/standby replication), rolling updates, backups, and failover
procedures. It integrates directly with the Kubernetes API, automating
the complex tasks that a human database administrator would normally
perform.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>CloudNativePG-17</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cnpg-17/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:30:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cnpg-17/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;CloudNativePG (CNPG) is a Kubernetes operator designed by PostgreSQL
experts to manage PostgreSQL database workloads natively on
Kubernetes. It covers the entire operational lifecycle, automatically
managing database deployment, high-availability configurations
(primary/standby replication), rolling updates, backups, and failover
procedures. It integrates directly with the Kubernetes API, automating
the complex tasks that a human database administrator would normally
perform.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>RabbitMQ Cluster Operator</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/rabbitmq-cluster-operator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:24:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/rabbitmq-cluster-operator/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The RabbitMQ Cluster Operator streamlines message broker operations by providing cloud-native orchestration capabilities
for RabbitMQ deployments. It enables teams to define cluster specifications through Kubernetes custom resources,
automatically handling complex tasks like node provisioning, federation setup, and persistent storage configuration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This operator ensures reliable message processing infrastructure by managing cluster topology, implementing backup
strategies, and facilitating seamless upgrades without service disruption. It integrates with Kubernetes networking and
security policies, making RabbitMQ clusters production-ready with minimal operational overhead.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Redis Exporter</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/redis-exporter/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:16:03 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/redis-exporter/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Redis Exporter is a specialized monitoring tool that bridges Redis databases with Prometheus-based observability
platforms. It continuously collects comprehensive metrics including memory usage, connection statistics, command
execution rates, and replication status from Redis instances.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The exporter transforms Redis INFO command output and custom queries into Prometheus-compatible metrics, enabling
detailed performance analysis and automated alerting. It supports both standalone Redis servers and clustered
deployments, making it essential for maintaining visibility into Redis infrastructure health and performance trends.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Redis Operator</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/redis-operator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:11:13 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/redis-operator/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Redis Operator is a cloud-native solution that automates the deployment and management of Redis instances on Kubernetes
platforms. It supports both standalone and clustered Redis configurations, handling complex operations like scaling,
backup, and failover through declarative Kubernetes resources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The operator integrates seamlessly with Kubernetes ecosystem tools and provides comprehensive monitoring through Redis
exporters. It enables teams to focus on application development while ensuring Redis infrastructure remains highly
available and optimally configured across cloud and on-premises environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apicast</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apicast/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:04:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apicast/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apicast is the core API gateway component of the 3scale API Management
platform. It is a high-performance, Nginx-based proxy that processes
and controls all inbound API traffic. It intercepts requests,
authenticates them against defined policies (like rate limits, access
keys, or JWTs), and routes them to the correct upstream service. It&amp;rsquo;s
designed to be deployed as a container, managing the secure and
observable flow of communication between API consumers and backend
services.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Redis Sentinel</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/redis-sentinel/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:58:05 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/redis-sentinel/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Redis Sentinel is a high availability solution that monitors Redis deployments and automatically handles failover
scenarios. It ensures continuous service by detecting master failures and promoting replicas through distributed
consensus among Sentinel nodes. Sentinel makes quorum-based decisions to maintain system integrity and prevent
split-brain situations.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Rocky 9</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/rocky-9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:39:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/rocky-9/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This image contains standard installation of Rocky Linux 9 operating system made for containerized workloads, it&amp;rsquo;s made
from &lt;code&gt;scratch&lt;/code&gt; image. Important notice - this image does not contain package manager &lt;code&gt;dnf&lt;/code&gt; and it uses &lt;code&gt;microdnf&lt;/code&gt; simplified
version of &lt;code&gt;dnf&lt;/code&gt; to install packages. If you need full &lt;code&gt;dnf&lt;/code&gt; package you can add it with the command:&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Rocky 9 Minimal</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/rocky-9-minimal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:34:34 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/rocky-9-minimal/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This image contains minimalistic installation of Rocky Linux 9 operating system made for containerized workloads, from
&lt;code&gt;scratch&lt;/code&gt; image. Important notice - this image does not contain package manager &lt;code&gt;dnf&lt;/code&gt; and it uses &lt;code&gt;microdnf&lt;/code&gt; simplified
version of &lt;code&gt;dnf&lt;/code&gt; to install packages. If you need full &lt;code&gt;dnf&lt;/code&gt; package you can add it with the command:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;pre tabindex="0" style="color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;"&gt;&lt;code class="language-bash" data-lang="bash"&gt;&lt;span style="display:flex;"&gt;&lt;span&gt;microdnf install dnf
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description></item><item><title>EZD-RP</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/ezd-rp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:48:34 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/ezd-rp/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Complete and ready-to-deploy set of software and tools, compatible
with the EZD RP application, necessary for its installation in your
own infrastructure, along with ongoing updates.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Elastic Agent</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/elastic-agent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:44:11 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/elastic-agent/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Elastic Agent is a versatile tool for collecting logs, metrics, and
performance data, integrating with Elastic Stack. It enables
performance monitoring and supports security by sending data to
Elasticsearch for analysis.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ArgoCD</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/argocd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:40:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/argocd/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;ArgoCD is a declarative, version-controlled application deployment
tool designed to automate and manage application configurations and
environments. It follows the GitOps pattern, utilizing Git
repositories as the source of truth for defining the desired
application state. Users can specify Kubernetes manifests using
various methods such as kustomize applications, Helm charts, JSONnet
files, or plain directories of YAML/json manifests. ArgoCD automates
the deployment process based on the desired application state defined
in Git repositories, making application deployment and lifecycle
management easy, auditable, and understandable.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Greenplum DB</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/greenplum-db/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:35:33 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/greenplum-db/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Greenplum Database (GPDB) is an open-source database optimized for
data analytics in distributed environments, utilizing a massively
parallel processing (MPP) architecture. It enables the simultaneous
processing of large datasets across multiple nodes, providing high
performance and scalability, and supports advanced business analytics
and big data processing.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GP Backup</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gpbackup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:30:13 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gpbackup/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GPBackup is an efficient tool for managing backups in Greenplum
Database. It allows the creation of full and incremental backups of
entire databases as well as selected tables. With advanced data
compression and segmentation, it ensures fast backup creation and the
ability to restore data to any point in time.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Sealed Secrets</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/sealed-secrets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:21:43 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/sealed-secrets/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Sealed Secret is a tool used in the Kubernetes ecosystem for securely
storing sensitive data, such as passwords or private keys.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>OceanBase</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/oceanbase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:18:19 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/oceanbase/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;OceanBase is a distributed, open-source relational database designed
to support high transactional and analytical workloads in the cloud.
It offers high availability, low latency and support for multiple
regions and thousands of nodes. It provides full SQL compatibility,
ACID transaction support and scalability, ideal for high-volume
applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GP Upgrade</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gpupgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:14:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gpupgrade/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GPUpgrade is an automation tool for upgrading Greenplum Database,
providing a fast and secure process for data migration and system
updates. It minimizes the risk of errors and downtime, supporting
software modernization and data conversion. It also offers monitoring
and rollback mechanisms, ensuring compliance and stability in
production systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>[X?] External Secrets</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/external-secrets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:07:34 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/external-secrets/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;External Secrets Operator is a tool for Kubernetes environments that
enables integration with various external secret management systems.
It operates by retrieving data from these external sources using their
APIs and automatically injecting this data into Kubernetes Secret
resources. Its goal is to facilitate the synchronization and
management of secrets between external systems and Kubernetes.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Harbor</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/harbor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:55:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/harbor/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Harbor operates as a platform enabling the management of container
repositories in Kubernetes environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Ruby</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/ruby/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:43:44 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/ruby/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Ruby stands as an easy-to-use, interpreted, dynamically-typed,
object-oriented, and universal programming language capable of
supporting multiple paradigms.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Elasticsearch</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/elasticsearch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:34:46 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/elasticsearch/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Elasticsearch is a powerful search and data analysis engine that
enables processing, indexing, and analysis of large datasets in
real-time. It functions as a central component of the Elastic Stack,
which also includes Kibana for data visualization and Logstash for log
processing. Elasticsearch is utilized in various fields such as log
analysis, IT infrastructure monitoring, business data analysis,
content searching, and information security.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Python</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/python/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:19:54 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/python/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Python stands as a dynamic and high-level programming language,
renowned for its versatility and readability, making it an excellent
choice for various applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>MongoDB</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/mongodb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:01:24 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/mongodb/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;MongoDB is a high-performance, document-oriented NoSQL database.
Instead of storing data in rigid tables and rows (like a relational
database), it stores data in flexible, JSON-like &amp;ldquo;documents&amp;rdquo; within
&amp;ldquo;collections.&amp;rdquo; This &amp;ldquo;schema-less&amp;rdquo; model allows developers to store and
combine data of any structure easily and dynamically change the data
model (schema) without application downtime. It&amp;rsquo;s built on a
distributed scale-out architecture, making it highly scalable and
popular for modern, data-intensive applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Jenkins</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jenkins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 20:49:27 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jenkins/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Jenkins is an open-source automation server used for continuous
integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD) pipelines, enabling
developers to automate building, testing, and deploying software.
Download our ready Helm Charts tailored for Jenkins.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GP Diskquota</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gp-diskquota/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 20:34:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gp-diskquota/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Diskquota is an extension that provides disk usage enforcement for
database objects in Greenplum DB. Currently it supports to set quota
limit on schema and role in a given database and limit the amount of
disk space that a schema or a role can use.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apache Camel K</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-camel-k/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 20:17:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-camel-k/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Camel K is a lightweight, Kubernetes-native version of Apache
Camel that enables rapid deployment of integrations in cloud-based
container environments. It automates application lifecycle processes,
making it easier to scale microservices and monitor integrations.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>PostgreSQL</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/postgresql/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 20:02:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/postgresql/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;PostgreSQL is acknowledged as a sophisticated Relational Database
Management System (RDBMS) renowned for its robust support of advanced
data types.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Trivy</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/trivy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 19:47:26 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/trivy/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Trivy is a vulnerability analysis tool for containers. It is a
vulnerability scanner that automatically scans container images and
reports discovered security vulnerabilities and other potential
threats.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Prometheus</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/prometheus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 19:20:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/prometheus/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Prometheus is a monitoring and alerting system widely used in cloud
and microservices environments. It is an open-source tool that enables
the collection of metrics from various components of IT
infrastructure, such as servers, containers, databases, etc.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Pgadmin</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/pgadmin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 19:06:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/pgadmin/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;pgAdmin functions as an open-source platform for administering and developing PostgreSQL.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Sonarqube</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/sonarqube/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:56:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/sonarqube/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;SonarQube operates as a platform for automatic code quality analysis.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kyverno</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kyverno/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:37:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kyverno/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Kyverno is an open source policy engine for Kubernetes, enabling the
definition, management, and enforcement of security and compliance
policies within a Kubernetes cluster.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Istio</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/istio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:30:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/istio/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Istio is a platform for managing traffic, securing, and monitoring
services in microservices environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ClickHouse</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/clickhouse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:31:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/clickhouse/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;ClickHouse is an open-source, columnar database specializing in
ultra-fast analytics and real-time processing of large data volumes.
Optimized for handling massive datasets, ClickHouse enables
lightning-fast execution of complex SQL queries, making it ideal for
companies focused on big data and business analytics. It supports
cluster processing, allowing efficient querying of distributed data
and real-time report generation.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Gpbackup S3</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gpbackup-s3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:20:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gpbackup-s3/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GPBackup-S3 is a tool for automatic backups of Greenplum Database with
Amazon S3 integration. It enables easy storage, restoration, and
verification of full and incremental backups in a secure, scalable
cloud. This is an ideal solution for organizations looking to
efficiently manage data in the cloud.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apache Karaf</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-karaf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:12:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-karaf/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Karaf is a lightweight OSGi container that enables easy
deployment, management, and updating of applications and services in
modular environments. It offers flexibility, dynamic module loading,
and clustering, making it an ideal solution for managing applications
in enterprise environments. Karaf is also ideal for Java applications,
enabling modular deployment and management of services in large and
complex environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Redis</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/redis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:56:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/redis/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Redis functions as an efficient, non-relational database management
system that stores data in a key-value structure within the primary
storage of the server, ensuring swift access to information.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apache Doris</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-doris/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:43:27 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-doris/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Doris is a distributed, open-source OLAP database optimized for
high performance and ease of use. With its MPP (Massively Parallel
Processing) model, it supports real-time analytical and operational
queries, making it ideal for big data applications, recommendation
systems, and business dashboards. Apache Doris offers
user-friendliness and integration with popular analytics tools,
enabling quick deployment and efficient report generation.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kibana</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kibana/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:19:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kibana/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Kibana is an advanced tool for data visualization and analysis,
serving as a key component in the Elastic Stack.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apache Camel Karavan</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-camel-karavan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:06:37 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-camel-karavan/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Camel Karavan is a visual extension of Apache Camel that
enables intuitive integration design using Enterprise Integration
Patterns (EIP) through a drag-and-drop interface. This makes it easier
for DevOps teams and developers to create complex data flows and
orchestrate processes, making it ideal for cloud and containerized
environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ActiveMQ</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-activemq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:56:03 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-activemq/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;ActiveMQ is an open-source message queuing system that supports
protocols such as JMS, STOMP, MQTT, and AMQP. It enables asynchronous
message exchange in distributed environments, providing reliability,
scalability, and ease of use. Ideal for cloud and microservice
applications, ActiveMQ offers high availability and support for
clustering and message replication, enabling the creation of
event-driven applications and system integration.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Gitea</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gitea/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:40:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gitea/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Gitea is a software including Git hosting, code review, team
collaboration, package registry and CI/CD.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Starrocks</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/starrocks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:34:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/starrocks/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;StarRocks is a modern MPP (Massively Parallel Processing) database
designed for advanced analytics with ultra-fast OLAP queries. It
enables simultaneous processing of historical and operational data,
making it ideal for applications requiring real-time analytics.
StarRocks combines the flexibility of NoSQL with the performance of
SQL, supporting various data formats and integrating with popular
analytics tools. It ensures high query performance and supports
complex analyses.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Nodejs</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nodejs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:24:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nodejs/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Node.js stands as a dynamic runtime environment, utilizing the V8
engine, specifically crafted for the development of contemporary,
interactive web applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Databend</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/databend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:18:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/databend/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Databend is an open-source, Rust-based cloud data warehouse offering
high performance for large datasets, with features like Time Travel,
Multi Catalog, and seamless scalability across various object storage
solutions.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>RabbitMQ</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/rabbitmq/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:32:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/rabbitmq/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;RabbitMQ is a sophisticated system for message queuing, serving as a
resilient intermediary solution that facilitates seamless
communication among different elements within distributed
applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GP pgbouncer</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gp-pgbouncer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:04:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gp-pgbouncer/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GP-pgBouncer is a lightweight connection proxy for Greenplum Database
that optimizes connection management through pooling, latency
reduction, and performance improvement. It enables better scalability
and access control in high-load environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GP PXF</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gp-pxf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 14:11:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gp-pxf/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;An extension for Greenplum Database that enables access to data from
various sources, such as HDFS, Amazon S3, and NoSQL databases, without
the need to transfer them. It supports data formats like CSV, Parquet,
and Avro, facilitating big data integration and analysis within a
single environment&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>CloudNative-PG</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cloudnativepg/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:28:54 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cloudnativepg/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;CloudNativePG (CNPG) is an open-source platform designed to seamlessly manage PostgreSQL databases
in Kubernetes environments. It covers the entire operational lifecycle—from deployment to ongoing
maintenance—through its core component, the CloudNativePG operator.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Neuvector</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/neuvector/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 11:34:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/neuvector/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;NeuVector is a platform for securing containers and microservices operating in cloud-based environments, including
Kubernetes clusters. It provides monitoring, threat detection, and security incident response capabilities. Download
our ready Helm Charts tailored for NeuVector.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Angular</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/angular/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 11:07:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/angular/</guid><description>&lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maintained by a dedicated team at Google, Angular provides a broad suite of tools, APIs, and libraries to simplify and
streamline your development workflow. Angular gives you a solid platform on which to build fast, reliable applications
that scale with both the size of your team and the size of your codebase.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apache Kafka</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-kafka/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:57:34 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-kafka/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Kafka is a distributed event store and stream-processing
platform. It is an open-source system developed by the Apache Software
Foundation written in Java and Scala.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apache Servicemix</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-servicemix/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:54:31 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-servicemix/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;</description></item><item><title>Cert-manager</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cert-manager/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:42:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cert-manager/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cert-manager is a Kubernetes tool that automates the issuance, renewal, and management of TLS certificates using various
providers like Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt. Download our ready Helm Charts tailored for KubeArmor.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Java</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/java/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:46:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/java/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Java is an advanced programming platform known for three key attributes: reliability, robust security measures, and the
ability to seamlessly transport code. It&amp;rsquo;s well known for its &amp;ldquo;write once, run anywhere&amp;rdquo; capability, allowing developers
to create applications that can operate across various devices and operating systems without modification.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are providing the most popular OpenJDK.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>