<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Database on Sourcemation</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/categories/database/</link><description>Recent content in Database on Sourcemation</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 02:10:43 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sourcemation.com/categories/database/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>MariaDB</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/mariadb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 02:10:43 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/mariadb/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;MariaDB is a popular open source relational database that was created by the
original developers of MySQL. It&amp;rsquo;s well known for better performance,
scalability, and having more features compared to MySQL, while being in most
cases a drop-in-replacement for MySQL. It&amp;rsquo;s managed by the MariaDB Foundation to
ensure its continued development as the real open source software. This image
use the official MariaDB packages and is optimized for container workloads.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Postgres 16</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/postgres-16/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 13:05:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/postgres-16/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PostgreSQL 16 represents a mature and battle-tested database solution that has evolved through decades of continuous
innovation and community contribution. This version combines advanced SQL capabilities with exceptional stability,
making it the preferred choice for mission-critical applications across industries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sourcemation&amp;rsquo;s PostgreSQL 16 distribution is compiled using our secure automated build system on the latest Debian 12
Slim foundation. Each build undergoes rigorous verification processes including cryptographic validation of source
materials, ensuring you receive a hardened and trustworthy database platform. Regular maintenance updates keep your
installation current with the latest security patches and performance improvements.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Postgres 17</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/postgres-17/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 13:03:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/postgres-17/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PostgreSQL stands as one of the most sophisticated open-source database systems available, offering enterprise-level
capabilities with over three decades of continuous development. Known for its exceptional reliability, extensibility,
and standards compliance, it supports both SQL relational and JSON non-relational querying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our PostgreSQL 17 container is meticulously built by Sourcemation&amp;rsquo;s automated infrastructure using the latest stable
release. Running on our optimized Debian 12 Slim base image, this distribution ensures minimal attack surface while
maintaining full functionality. The build pipeline includes cryptographic verification of all source components,
delivering a secure and trustworthy database solution for production environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>CloudNativePG-16</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cnpg-16/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:30:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cnpg-16/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;CloudNativePG (CNPG) is a Kubernetes operator designed by PostgreSQL
experts to manage PostgreSQL database workloads natively on
Kubernetes. It covers the entire operational lifecycle, automatically
managing database deployment, high-availability configurations
(primary/standby replication), rolling updates, backups, and failover
procedures. It integrates directly with the Kubernetes API, automating
the complex tasks that a human database administrator would normally
perform.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>CloudNativePG-17</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cnpg-17/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:30:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cnpg-17/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;CloudNativePG (CNPG) is a Kubernetes operator designed by PostgreSQL
experts to manage PostgreSQL database workloads natively on
Kubernetes. It covers the entire operational lifecycle, automatically
managing database deployment, high-availability configurations
(primary/standby replication), rolling updates, backups, and failover
procedures. It integrates directly with the Kubernetes API, automating
the complex tasks that a human database administrator would normally
perform.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Redis Operator</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/redis-operator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:11:13 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/redis-operator/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Redis Operator is a cloud-native solution that automates the deployment and management of Redis instances on Kubernetes
platforms. It supports both standalone and clustered Redis configurations, handling complex operations like scaling,
backup, and failover through declarative Kubernetes resources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The operator integrates seamlessly with Kubernetes ecosystem tools and provides comprehensive monitoring through Redis
exporters. It enables teams to focus on application development while ensuring Redis infrastructure remains highly
available and optimally configured across cloud and on-premises environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Redis Sentinel</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/redis-sentinel/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:58:05 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/redis-sentinel/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Redis Sentinel is a high availability solution that monitors Redis deployments and automatically handles failover
scenarios. It ensures continuous service by detecting master failures and promoting replicas through distributed
consensus among Sentinel nodes. Sentinel makes quorum-based decisions to maintain system integrity and prevent
split-brain situations.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>EZD-RP</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/ezd-rp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:48:34 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/ezd-rp/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Complete and ready-to-deploy set of software and tools, compatible
with the EZD RP application, necessary for its installation in your
own infrastructure, along with ongoing updates.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Greenplum DB</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/greenplum-db/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:35:33 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/greenplum-db/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Greenplum Database (GPDB) is an open-source database optimized for
data analytics in distributed environments, utilizing a massively
parallel processing (MPP) architecture. It enables the simultaneous
processing of large datasets across multiple nodes, providing high
performance and scalability, and supports advanced business analytics
and big data processing.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GP Backup</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gpbackup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:30:13 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gpbackup/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GPBackup is an efficient tool for managing backups in Greenplum
Database. It allows the creation of full and incremental backups of
entire databases as well as selected tables. With advanced data
compression and segmentation, it ensures fast backup creation and the
ability to restore data to any point in time.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>OceanBase</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/oceanbase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:18:19 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/oceanbase/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;OceanBase is a distributed, open-source relational database designed
to support high transactional and analytical workloads in the cloud.
It offers high availability, low latency and support for multiple
regions and thousands of nodes. It provides full SQL compatibility,
ACID transaction support and scalability, ideal for high-volume
applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GP Upgrade</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gpupgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:14:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gpupgrade/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GPUpgrade is an automation tool for upgrading Greenplum Database,
providing a fast and secure process for data migration and system
updates. It minimizes the risk of errors and downtime, supporting
software modernization and data conversion. It also offers monitoring
and rollback mechanisms, ensuring compliance and stability in
production systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Elasticsearch</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/elasticsearch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:34:46 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/elasticsearch/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Elasticsearch is a powerful search and data analysis engine that
enables processing, indexing, and analysis of large datasets in
real-time. It functions as a central component of the Elastic Stack,
which also includes Kibana for data visualization and Logstash for log
processing. Elasticsearch is utilized in various fields such as log
analysis, IT infrastructure monitoring, business data analysis,
content searching, and information security.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>MongoDB</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/mongodb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:01:24 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/mongodb/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;MongoDB is a high-performance, document-oriented NoSQL database.
Instead of storing data in rigid tables and rows (like a relational
database), it stores data in flexible, JSON-like &amp;ldquo;documents&amp;rdquo; within
&amp;ldquo;collections.&amp;rdquo; This &amp;ldquo;schema-less&amp;rdquo; model allows developers to store and
combine data of any structure easily and dynamically change the data
model (schema) without application downtime. It&amp;rsquo;s built on a
distributed scale-out architecture, making it highly scalable and
popular for modern, data-intensive applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GP Diskquota</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gp-diskquota/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 20:34:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gp-diskquota/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Diskquota is an extension that provides disk usage enforcement for
database objects in Greenplum DB. Currently it supports to set quota
limit on schema and role in a given database and limit the amount of
disk space that a schema or a role can use.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>PostgreSQL</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/postgresql/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 20:02:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/postgresql/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;PostgreSQL is acknowledged as a sophisticated Relational Database
Management System (RDBMS) renowned for its robust support of advanced
data types.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Prometheus</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/prometheus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 19:20:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/prometheus/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Prometheus is a monitoring and alerting system widely used in cloud
and microservices environments. It is an open-source tool that enables
the collection of metrics from various components of IT
infrastructure, such as servers, containers, databases, etc.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Pgadmin</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/pgadmin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 19:06:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/pgadmin/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;pgAdmin functions as an open-source platform for administering and developing PostgreSQL.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ClickHouse</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/clickhouse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:31:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/clickhouse/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;ClickHouse is an open-source, columnar database specializing in
ultra-fast analytics and real-time processing of large data volumes.
Optimized for handling massive datasets, ClickHouse enables
lightning-fast execution of complex SQL queries, making it ideal for
companies focused on big data and business analytics. It supports
cluster processing, allowing efficient querying of distributed data
and real-time report generation.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GPBackup-S3</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gpbackup-s3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:20:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gpbackup-s3/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GPBackup-S3 is a tool for automatic backups of Greenplum Database with
Amazon S3 integration. It enables easy storage, restoration, and
verification of full and incremental backups in a secure, scalable
cloud. This is an ideal solution for organizations looking to
efficiently manage data in the cloud.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Redis</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/redis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:56:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/redis/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Redis functions as an efficient, non-relational database management
system that stores data in a key-value structure within the primary
storage of the server, ensuring swift access to information.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apache Doris</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-doris/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:43:27 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-doris/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Doris is a distributed, open-source OLAP database optimized for
high performance and ease of use. With its MPP (Massively Parallel
Processing) model, it supports real-time analytical and operational
queries, making it ideal for big data applications, recommendation
systems, and business dashboards. Apache Doris offers
user-friendliness and integration with popular analytics tools,
enabling quick deployment and efficient report generation.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Starrocks</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/starrocks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:34:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/starrocks/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;StarRocks is a modern MPP (Massively Parallel Processing) database
designed for advanced analytics with ultra-fast OLAP queries. It
enables simultaneous processing of historical and operational data,
making it ideal for applications requiring real-time analytics.
StarRocks combines the flexibility of NoSQL with the performance of
SQL, supporting various data formats and integrating with popular
analytics tools. It ensures high query performance and supports
complex analyses.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Databend</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/databend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:18:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/databend/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Databend is an open-source, Rust-based cloud data warehouse offering
high performance for large datasets, with features like Time Travel,
Multi Catalog, and seamless scalability across various object storage
solutions.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GP pgbouncer</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gp-pgbouncer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:04:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gp-pgbouncer/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GP-pgBouncer is a lightweight connection proxy for Greenplum Database
that optimizes connection management through pooling, latency
reduction, and performance improvement. It enables better scalability
and access control in high-load environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GP PXF</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gp-pxf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 14:11:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gp-pxf/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;An extension for Greenplum Database that enables access to data from
various sources, such as HDFS, Amazon S3, and NoSQL databases, without
the need to transfer them. It supports data formats like CSV, Parquet,
and Avro, facilitating big data integration and analysis within a
single environment&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>CloudNative-PG</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cloudnativepg/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:28:54 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cloudnativepg/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;CloudNativePG (CNPG) is an open-source platform designed to seamlessly manage PostgreSQL databases
in Kubernetes environments. It covers the entire operational lifecycle—from deployment to ongoing
maintenance—through its core component, the CloudNativePG operator.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>