<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Utils on Sourcemation</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/categories/utils/</link><description>Recent content in Utils on Sourcemation</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 17:03:17 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sourcemation.com/categories/utils/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>JDK 17</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jdk-17/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 17:03:17 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jdk-17/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based on the official OpenJDK Java Development Kit for the Java 17 Long-Term
Support (LTS) release, designed for application developers. It includes all the
tools needed to compile, run, and debug Java applications, such as the javac
compiler and the Java Virtual Machine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JDK 17&amp;rsquo;s end of life date is 31st October 2027, making it a suitable choice for
users seeking a platform to run not only new but also existing applications that
require long-term stability and support.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>JRE 17</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jre-17/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 17:03:17 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jre-17/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based on the official OpenJDK JRE for the Java 17 Long-Term Support (LTS)
release, designed for application runtimes. It includes all the tools needed to run Java applications, such as the Java Virtual Machine (JVM), core libraries, and standard utilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JDK/JRE 17 end of life date is 31st October 2027, making it a suitable choice for
users seeking a platform to run not only new but also existing applications that
require long-term stability and support.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Matomo</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/matomo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 14:39:08 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/matomo/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Matomo is a leading open-source web analytics platform that is well-known for
respecting user privacy and data ownership. This type of analytics is an
ethical and compliant choice for website owners who want to gain insights into
their visitors without compromising their privacy and leaking their data to
third parties like Google Analytics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This single container image of Matomo is designed for easy deployment in
various environments, including Docker, Kubernetes, and thus OpenShift and
Rancher. It requires access to a separate database like MySQL or MariaDB to
store analytical data.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>OpenLDAP</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/openldap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 14:39:04 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/openldap/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;OpenLDAP is the most popular open-source implementation of the Lightweight
Directory Access Protocol (LDAP). It contains all administrator goodies like a
load balancer/proxy, libraries, clients and of course the server itself.
OpenLDAP is managed and developed by the OpenLDAP Foundation. OpenLDAP has a
BSD-style license - the OpenLDAP Public License.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The OpenLDAP project started from code from the University of Michigan, the
first release was just cleaned up code from their implementation of LDAP. Over
the years OpenLDAP has grown and now is the de facto standard for LDAP
implementations on Linux and other Unix-like operating systems. The LDAP
protocol is used for directory services and authentication, and it is widely
used in both educational and corporate environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>WordPress</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/wordpress/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 10:48:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/wordpress/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;WordPress is the world&amp;rsquo;s most popular website builder and content management
system (CMS). It is powering over 40% of all websites on the Internet (2025).
WordPress is built on PHP and can use MySQL or MariaDB as its database backend.
WordPress is simple, user-friendly, feature-rich and highly customizable.
Built-in user management, content management, media support, and SEO tools make
it great choice for bloggers, businesses, non-profits but also large
enterprises.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ZooKeeper</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/zookeeper/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 01:54:41 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/zookeeper/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache ZooKeeper is a well-known high-performance, centralized service
providing coordination primitives. It&amp;rsquo;s frequently used with distributed
applications, as all of them need this kind of synchronization in one form or
another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The most important features provided by ZooKeeper include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Synchronization: Reliable way to coordinate access to shared resources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Configuration: Centralized service for configuration management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Naming: Distributed naming registry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Group Services: Facilitates group membership and leader/followers election.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ZooKeeper is engineered with ultra large-scale systems, that require high
throughput, low latency, fault-tolerance, and high availability.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Git</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/git/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:52:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/git/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Git is well-known as &amp;ldquo;the stupid content tracker&amp;rdquo; made by Linus Torvalds after
problems with BitKeeper licensing in early 2000s. It was designed to be fast,
efficient, and capable of handling large projects with ease - as Linux kernel
itself is one of the biggest open source projects ever created. Today git is
de-facto standard for version control in software development, with a vast
ecosystem of plugins, integrations, and hosting services built around it.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>External Dns</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/external-dns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 01:45:27 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/external-dns/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This is the official Sourcemation Docker image for ExternalDNS, a Kubernetes
addon that works with various DNS providers to manage DNS records dynamically
based on the resources in your cluster. The list of supported providers is
extensive, including the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AWS Route 53&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AzureDNS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CloudFlare&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Cloud DNS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DigitalOcean&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CoreDNS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OVHcloud&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scaleway&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and many more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our external-DNS is compiled from the source provided by the Kubernetes Special
Interest Group (SIG) team.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Hugo</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/hugo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 14:05:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/hugo/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hugo is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most popular open-source static site generators (SSGs),
written in the Go programming language. It is renowned for its blazing-fast
build speeds, often rendering even large, complex websites in a fraction of
a second. Hugo takes content written in markdown, processes it through
a powerful templating engine, and generates a complete, ready-to-deploy
static website (HTML, CSS, JS). Its robust feature set includes a built-in
asset pipeline (Hugo Pipes), flexible content and data modeling, and native
support for fetching content from external APIs, making it a versatile tool
for everything from simple blogs to large corporate websites.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Nginx Stable</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nginx-stable/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 14:33:46 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nginx-stable/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nginx Stable delivers enterprise-grade web serving capabilities with a focus on long-term reliability and consistent
performance across production environments. This stable branch undergoes extensive testing and validation, making it the
preferred choice for mission-critical applications that prioritize stability over cutting-edge features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The stable release branch receives only critical bug fixes and security updates, ensuring predictable behavior and
minimal risk of unexpected changes in production deployments. This approach makes it particularly well-suited for
enterprise environments where stability and reliability take precedence.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Nginx Mainline</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nginx-mainline/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 14:31:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nginx-mainline/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nginx Mainline represents the cutting-edge branch of the world&amp;rsquo;s most popular web server, delivering advanced HTTP
serving, reverse proxy functionality, and sophisticated load balancing capabilities. This version provides access to the
newest features and optimizations as they&amp;rsquo;re developed, making it ideal for environments that require the latest
innovations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Known for its exceptional performance characteristics and minimal resource consumption, Nginx excels at handling
high-concurrency scenarios while maintaining rock-solid stability. The mainline branch receives continuous updates with
new features, protocol improvements, and performance enhancements.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Mosquitto</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/mosquitto/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 14:26:38 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/mosquitto/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eclipse Mosquitto is a widely-adopted open-source MQTT broker that serves as the backbone for countless IoT deployments
worldwide. Developed under the Eclipse Foundation, it implements the MQTT protocol versions 5.0, 3.1.1, and 3.1, making
it compatible with virtually any MQTT client application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The broker is renowned for its lightweight architecture and exceptional performance, capable of handling thousands of
concurrent connections while maintaining minimal memory usage. Mosquitto supports advanced features including message
persistence, SSL/TLS encryption, bridge connections, and flexible authentication mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Openapi Generator CLI</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/openapi-generator-cli/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 13:11:55 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/openapi-generator-cli/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The OpenAPI Generator CLI is a powerful command-line utility that automates the creation of client libraries, server
stubs, and API documentation from OpenAPI specifications. This tool significantly accelerates development workflows by
generating consistent, well-structured code across multiple programming languages and frameworks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sourcemation&amp;rsquo;s distribution comes pre-configured with a secure user environment and includes an enhanced CLI script for
simplified version management. The container is built with security best practices, running under a non-root user
account to minimize potential attack vectors. Our automated build process ensures you receive the latest stable release
with all necessary dependencies properly configured for immediate use.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>JRE-21</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jre-21/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:31:38 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jre-21/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;JRE 21 is the Java Runtime Environment derived from the JDK 21
Long-Term Support (LTS) release, and it&amp;rsquo;s intended for end-users or
servers that only need to run pre-compiled Java applications. It
contains the core components, primarily the Java Virtual Machine (JVM)
and core class libraries, but omits development tools like the
compiler (javac). Any application running on JRE 21 gains the benefits
of the JDK 21 platform, including the performance improvements from
the finalization of Virtual Threads and other new language features.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>JDK-21</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jdk-21/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:31:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jdk-21/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;JDK 21 is the official Java Development Kit for the Java 21 Long-Term
Support (LTS) release, designed for application developers. It
includes all the tools needed to compile, debug, and run Java
applications, such as the javac compiler and the Java Virtual Machine.
This version is critically important as it finalizes several major
features from Project Loom, most notably Virtual Threads, which
fundamentally simplifies the development of high-throughput concurrent
applications. It also introduces other key features like Sequenced
Collections, Scoped Values, and enhanced Pattern Matching.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Micronaut</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/micronaut/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:08:47 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/micronaut/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Description: Micronaut is a modern, full-stack framework for the JVM
(supporting Java, Kotlin, and Groovy) designed specifically for
building modular microservices and serverless applications. Its key
differentiator is that it performs dependency injection,
configuration, and aspect-oriented programming at compile time
(Ahead-of-Time compilation) rather than at runtime using reflection.
This results in dramatically faster startup times, a much lower memory
footprint, and makes it an ideal choice for serverless functions and
containerized microservices.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Maven</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/maven/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:03:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/maven/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Maven is a foundational software project management and build
automation tool. Using a central XML configuration file (the pom.xml),
Maven manages all project dependencies (downloading required libraries
from repositories) and executes a standardized build lifecycle (e.g.,
compile, test, package, install, deploy). This
convention-over-configuration approach simplifies the build process,
making it reproducible and standard across all Java-based projects.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Manageiq</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/manageiq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:59:42 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/manageiq/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;ManageIQ is an open-source cloud management platform (CMP) that
provides a single interface for managing hybrid IT environments. It
discovers and monitors resources across disparate virtualization (like
VMware), private cloud (like OpenStack), and public cloud (like AWS,
Azure) platforms, as well as container platforms like Kubernetes. Its
key features include &amp;ldquo;Insight&amp;rdquo; (discovery, monitoring, analytics),
&amp;ldquo;Control&amp;rdquo; (security, compliance, policy enforcement), and &amp;ldquo;Automate&amp;rdquo;
(provisioning workflows, orchestration). It essentially acts as a
&amp;ldquo;manager of managers,&amp;rdquo; giving administrators a single pane of glass
for governance and automation.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kubectl</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kubectl/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:55:26 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kubectl/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;kubectl is the primary command-line interface (CLI) used to
communicate with and manage a Kubernetes cluster. It communicates with
the Kubernetes API server to execute commands. Administrators and
developers use this utility for nearly all cluster operations,
including deploying applications (using .yaml manifests), checking the
status and logs of running pods (observability), managing node health,
and configuring all Kubernetes resources like services, deployments,
and secrets.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kong</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:47:31 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kong/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Kong is a cloud-native API gateway and platform built on top of Nginx
(specifically OpenResty). It is deployed in front of backend
microservices to act as a single, controllable entry point for all API
traffic. Its core function is to provide a comprehensive security and
management layer, handling tasks like authentication (OAuth2, JWT),
authorization, rate limiting, and traffic transformation via a
&amp;ldquo;plugin&amp;rdquo; architecture. By intercepting and proxying all requests, Kong
also provides critical observability metrics, logs, and traces for
monitoring API performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Helidon</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/helidon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:33:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/helidon/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Helidon is an open-source, cloud-native set of Java libraries from
Oracle for building microservices. It provides two distinct paths for
development. Helidon SE is a lightweight, &amp;ldquo;reactive&amp;rdquo; toolkit that uses
a functional, non-blocking approach (built on Netty) for maximum
performance and a small footprint. Helidon MP is a full implementation
of the Eclipse MicroProfile specification, providing a more
declarative, annotation-driven programming model (similar to Spring
Boot or Micronaut) for enterprise Java developers.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GCC-13</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gcc-13/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:41:14 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gcc-13/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GCC 13, the GNU Compiler Collection, is the foundational toolchain for
most Linux systems. This version significantly expanded its language
support by introducing an initial front-end for the Rust programming
language. It also solidified its C++ support by completing many C++20
features and introducing initial capabilities from the C++23 standard.
As a critical component, it takes source code from these languages
(plus C, Fortran, etc.) and translates it into optimized machine code,
while adding improved static analysis tools (like SARIF diagnostics)
for all developers.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GCC-14</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gcc-14/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:41:14 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gcc-14/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GCC 14, the GNU Compiler Collection, continues its role as the core
compiler for the GNU project. This release is notable for its
significant progress on the C++23 standard, implementing new features
like static operator() and import std;. It also enhances its support
for modern hardware, introducing improved code generation for new Arm
and RISC-V processor extensions, and expands its parallelism
capabilities with deeper support for the OpenMP 5.1 and 5.2 standards.
It translates human-readable source code into the optimized machine
code required for all open-source compilation.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GCC-15</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gcc-15/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:41:14 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gcc-15/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GCC 15, the GNU Compiler Collection, serves as the critical compiler
toolchain for most Linux distributions. This version marks a major
milestone by officially changing the default C language standard from
GNU17 to GNU23. It also dramatically expands its language support by
introducing a new front-end for the COBOL programming language. As a
core component of open-source development, it translates source code
into optimized machine code while providing powerful new features like
incremental Link-Time Optimization (LTO) to speed up builds.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GCC-16</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gcc-16/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:41:14 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gcc-16/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GCC 16, representing the current development trunk of the GNU Compiler
Collection, is the next major iteration of the foundational
open-source toolchain. As the default compiler for the Linux
ecosystem, its development is focused on pushing language standards
forward, primarily by introducing experimental support for the
upcoming C++26 standard (such as std::function_ref). It continues to
be the critical utility that translates human-readable C, C++, and
other languages into the optimized machine code that powers the
open-source world, with a focus on new optimization techniques and
hardware support.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>CloudNativePG-16</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cnpg-16/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:30:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cnpg-16/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;CloudNativePG (CNPG) is a Kubernetes operator designed by PostgreSQL
experts to manage PostgreSQL database workloads natively on
Kubernetes. It covers the entire operational lifecycle, automatically
managing database deployment, high-availability configurations
(primary/standby replication), rolling updates, backups, and failover
procedures. It integrates directly with the Kubernetes API, automating
the complex tasks that a human database administrator would normally
perform.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>CloudNativePG-17</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cnpg-17/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:30:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cnpg-17/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;CloudNativePG (CNPG) is a Kubernetes operator designed by PostgreSQL
experts to manage PostgreSQL database workloads natively on
Kubernetes. It covers the entire operational lifecycle, automatically
managing database deployment, high-availability configurations
(primary/standby replication), rolling updates, backups, and failover
procedures. It integrates directly with the Kubernetes API, automating
the complex tasks that a human database administrator would normally
perform.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>RabbitMQ Cluster Operator</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/rabbitmq-cluster-operator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:24:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/rabbitmq-cluster-operator/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The RabbitMQ Cluster Operator streamlines message broker operations by providing cloud-native orchestration capabilities
for RabbitMQ deployments. It enables teams to define cluster specifications through Kubernetes custom resources,
automatically handling complex tasks like node provisioning, federation setup, and persistent storage configuration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This operator ensures reliable message processing infrastructure by managing cluster topology, implementing backup
strategies, and facilitating seamless upgrades without service disruption. It integrates with Kubernetes networking and
security policies, making RabbitMQ clusters production-ready with minimal operational overhead.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apicast</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apicast/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:04:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apicast/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apicast is the core API gateway component of the 3scale API Management
platform. It is a high-performance, Nginx-based proxy that processes
and controls all inbound API traffic. It intercepts requests,
authenticates them against defined policies (like rate limits, access
keys, or JWTs), and routes them to the correct upstream service. It&amp;rsquo;s
designed to be deployed as a container, managing the secure and
observable flow of communication between API consumers and backend
services.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>EZD-RP</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/ezd-rp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:48:34 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/ezd-rp/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Complete and ready-to-deploy set of software and tools, compatible
with the EZD RP application, necessary for its installation in your
own infrastructure, along with ongoing updates.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Elastic Agent</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/elastic-agent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:44:11 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/elastic-agent/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Elastic Agent is a versatile tool for collecting logs, metrics, and
performance data, integrating with Elastic Stack. It enables
performance monitoring and supports security by sending data to
Elasticsearch for analysis.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ArgoCD</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/argocd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:40:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/argocd/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;ArgoCD is a declarative, version-controlled application deployment
tool designed to automate and manage application configurations and
environments. It follows the GitOps pattern, utilizing Git
repositories as the source of truth for defining the desired
application state. Users can specify Kubernetes manifests using
various methods such as kustomize applications, Helm charts, JSONnet
files, or plain directories of YAML/json manifests. ArgoCD automates
the deployment process based on the desired application state defined
in Git repositories, making application deployment and lifecycle
management easy, auditable, and understandable.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GP Backup</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gpbackup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:30:13 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gpbackup/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GPBackup is an efficient tool for managing backups in Greenplum
Database. It allows the creation of full and incremental backups of
entire databases as well as selected tables. With advanced data
compression and segmentation, it ensures fast backup creation and the
ability to restore data to any point in time.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Sealed Secrets</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/sealed-secrets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:21:43 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/sealed-secrets/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Sealed Secret is a tool used in the Kubernetes ecosystem for securely
storing sensitive data, such as passwords or private keys.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GP Upgrade</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gpupgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:14:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gpupgrade/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GPUpgrade is an automation tool for upgrading Greenplum Database,
providing a fast and secure process for data migration and system
updates. It minimizes the risk of errors and downtime, supporting
software modernization and data conversion. It also offers monitoring
and rollback mechanisms, ensuring compliance and stability in
production systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Harbor</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/harbor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:55:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/harbor/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Harbor operates as a platform enabling the management of container
repositories in Kubernetes environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Jenkins</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jenkins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 20:49:27 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/jenkins/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Jenkins is an open-source automation server used for continuous
integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD) pipelines, enabling
developers to automate building, testing, and deploying software.
Download our ready Helm Charts tailored for Jenkins.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GP Diskquota</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gp-diskquota/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 20:34:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gp-diskquota/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Diskquota is an extension that provides disk usage enforcement for
database objects in Greenplum DB. Currently it supports to set quota
limit on schema and role in a given database and limit the amount of
disk space that a schema or a role can use.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apache Camel K</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-camel-k/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 20:17:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-camel-k/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Camel K is a lightweight, Kubernetes-native version of Apache
Camel that enables rapid deployment of integrations in cloud-based
container environments. It automates application lifecycle processes,
making it easier to scale microservices and monitor integrations.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Trivy</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/trivy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 19:47:26 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/trivy/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Trivy is a vulnerability analysis tool for containers. It is a
vulnerability scanner that automatically scans container images and
reports discovered security vulnerabilities and other potential
threats.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Prometheus</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/prometheus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 19:20:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/prometheus/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Prometheus is a monitoring and alerting system widely used in cloud
and microservices environments. It is an open-source tool that enables
the collection of metrics from various components of IT
infrastructure, such as servers, containers, databases, etc.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Pgadmin</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/pgadmin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 19:06:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/pgadmin/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;pgAdmin functions as an open-source platform for administering and developing PostgreSQL.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Sonarqube</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/sonarqube/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:56:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/sonarqube/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;SonarQube operates as a platform for automatic code quality analysis.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kyverno</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kyverno/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:37:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kyverno/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Kyverno is an open source policy engine for Kubernetes, enabling the
definition, management, and enforcement of security and compliance
policies within a Kubernetes cluster.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Istio</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/istio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:30:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/istio/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Istio is a platform for managing traffic, securing, and monitoring
services in microservices environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GPBackup-S3</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gpbackup-s3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:20:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gpbackup-s3/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GPBackup-S3 is a tool for automatic backups of Greenplum Database with
Amazon S3 integration. It enables easy storage, restoration, and
verification of full and incremental backups in a secure, scalable
cloud. This is an ideal solution for organizations looking to
efficiently manage data in the cloud.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apache Karaf</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-karaf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:12:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-karaf/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Karaf is a lightweight OSGi container that enables easy
deployment, management, and updating of applications and services in
modular environments. It offers flexibility, dynamic module loading,
and clustering, making it an ideal solution for managing applications
in enterprise environments. Karaf is also ideal for Java applications,
enabling modular deployment and management of services in large and
complex environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Redis</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/redis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:56:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/redis/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Redis functions as an efficient, non-relational database management
system that stores data in a key-value structure within the primary
storage of the server, ensuring swift access to information.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kibana</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kibana/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:19:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/kibana/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Kibana is an advanced tool for data visualization and analysis,
serving as a key component in the Elastic Stack.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apache Camel Karavan</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-camel-karavan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:06:37 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-camel-karavan/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Camel Karavan is a visual extension of Apache Camel that
enables intuitive integration design using Enterprise Integration
Patterns (EIP) through a drag-and-drop interface. This makes it easier
for DevOps teams and developers to create complex data flows and
orchestrate processes, making it ideal for cloud and containerized
environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ActiveMQ</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-activemq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:56:03 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-activemq/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;ActiveMQ is an open-source message queuing system that supports
protocols such as JMS, STOMP, MQTT, and AMQP. It enables asynchronous
message exchange in distributed environments, providing reliability,
scalability, and ease of use. Ideal for cloud and microservice
applications, ActiveMQ offers high availability and support for
clustering and message replication, enabling the creation of
event-driven applications and system integration.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Gitea</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gitea/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:40:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gitea/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Gitea is a software including Git hosting, code review, team
collaboration, package registry and CI/CD.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Nodejs</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nodejs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:24:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/nodejs/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Node.js stands as a dynamic runtime environment, utilizing the V8
engine, specifically crafted for the development of contemporary,
interactive web applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>RabbitMQ</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/rabbitmq/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:32:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/rabbitmq/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;RabbitMQ is a sophisticated system for message queuing, serving as a
resilient intermediary solution that facilitates seamless
communication among different elements within distributed
applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>GP pgbouncer</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gp-pgbouncer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:04:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/gp-pgbouncer/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;GP-pgBouncer is a lightweight connection proxy for Greenplum Database
that optimizes connection management through pooling, latency
reduction, and performance improvement. It enables better scalability
and access control in high-load environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>CloudNative-PG</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cloudnativepg/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:28:54 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cloudnativepg/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;CloudNativePG (CNPG) is an open-source platform designed to seamlessly manage PostgreSQL databases
in Kubernetes environments. It covers the entire operational lifecycle—from deployment to ongoing
maintenance—through its core component, the CloudNativePG operator.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Angular</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/angular/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 11:07:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/angular/</guid><description>&lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maintained by a dedicated team at Google, Angular provides a broad suite of tools, APIs, and libraries to simplify and
streamline your development workflow. Angular gives you a solid platform on which to build fast, reliable applications
that scale with both the size of your team and the size of your codebase.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apache Kafka</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-kafka/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:57:34 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-kafka/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Kafka is a distributed event store and stream-processing
platform. It is an open-source system developed by the Apache Software
Foundation written in Java and Scala.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apache Servicemix</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-servicemix/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:54:31 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/apache-servicemix/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;</description></item><item><title>Cert-manager</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cert-manager/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:42:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/cert-manager/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="description"&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cert-manager is a Kubernetes tool that automates the issuance, renewal, and management of TLS certificates using various
providers like Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt. Download our ready Helm Charts tailored for KubeArmor.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Java</title><link>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/java/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:46:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sourcemation.com/catalog/java/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Java is an advanced programming platform known for three key attributes: reliability, robust security measures, and the
ability to seamlessly transport code. It&amp;rsquo;s well known for its &amp;ldquo;write once, run anywhere&amp;rdquo; capability, allowing developers
to create applications that can operate across various devices and operating systems without modification.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are providing the most popular OpenJDK.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>